

Sumaer Jolly

Profile

Full-stack Developer well versed in business research and strategy. Have been learning how to code from Microverse the school for remote software developers since April 2019. Have also learnt Sketch App. Curious about new technologies and startups and always like to learn new things.

Employment History

Side Project at The Gyst Newsletter, New Delhi

December 2019 — Present

We are a daily email that curates and delivers the top business and tech news from India in a way that's informative and entertaining. Think of it as Morning Brew for India. Decided to work on this a side project after searching for an Indian Morning Brew equivalent for some time. Still early days but am up to 245 subscribers with open rates of > 50% daily.

Cofounder & CEO at Schooller Software Pvt Ltd, New Delhi

April 2018 — March 2019

Schooller is the only solution you need to run your daycare or preschool. Through Schooller you can easily run your centre, manage your classroom and engage with families.

User Research, Ideation and complete design and development of the android, iOS & web platform. Post building the Minimum Viable Product got Schooller to be used in 5 schools by going out and convincing these schools by just showing up and asking them to use it.

Head Of Smartventure at Smartworks, Gurgaon

November 2016 — March 2018

Was the 4th employee at Smartworks and the first in Delhi/NCR which was their head office. Helped grow the overall team from 4 to 85 employees when I left. Was actively involved in all parts of running Delhi operations including hiring, strategy ,marketing , setting policies and helping the founders with fundraising. Smartworks was the 2nd largest co-working space in India at the time I left.

Trainee at IIFL Wealth, New Delhi

August 2015 — September 2016

For the duration of my training period I worked under the director at the family office desk, learning about various aspects of corporate finance and analytics. In the latter part of my training period I was put into customer acquisition(sales) where I had to meet select ultra HNI(High Net Worth) clients and discuss their investment needs and accordingly advise them. At the end of my training period had lead to the acquisition of clients with a total corpus of Rs 100 crore.

College Intern at Jabong, Gurgaon

July 2014 — August 2014

Details

+919717009559

sumaerjolly@gmail.com

Skills

Product Development

HTML & CSS

JavaScript

React

Ruby

Ruby on Rails

Redux

UI/UX Design

Sketch App

Business Development

Market Research

Hobbies

Reading, Boxing and all things startups

Links

Github

Linkedin

Newsletter

Worked in Special Projects and was a part of the marketing and promotional team for Jabong Online Fashion Week. Was in charge of their social media marketing team and handled their Twitter and Facebook handle.

Education

Full Stack Web, Microverse Remote School for Software Developers, Remote

April 2019 — Present

Acquired a comprehensive array of full-stack and remote development skills:

- Remote pair programming
- Git flow
- Test-driven development
- Algorithms and data structure

Bsc Economics & Management, Singapore Institute Of Management, Singapore

July 2012 — July 2015

Degree was affiliated to the University Of London. Studied subjects like microeconomics, macroeconomics, Strategy & Corporate Finance.